翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
So we've covered the right half of the puzzle, primitive types.
我们已经讨论了谜题的右半部分，基本类型
Now what we're going to do is turn over to the left half of the walrus mystery,
现在转到海象之谜的左半部分
how the walrus behaves, by talking about so-called reference types.
通过海象的行为谈论所谓的引用类型
So we've said there are eight primitive types in Java, byte, short, int, long, et cetera.
之前说过 Java 有8种基本类型 byte、short、int、long 等等
And any other variable you declare, say, a planet or a walrus or an int array,
以及你声明的任何其他变量，比方说行星、海象或整型数组
is going to be a so-called reference type.
后者是所谓的引用类型
That's just the term for all of the types that are not these.
引用类型就是非基本类型的术语
So let's start digging into our understanding of reference types by discussing object instantiations.
让我们从对象实例化开始深入理解引用类型
So whenever you say new dog or new walrus or new planet or whatever,
每次 new 狗或 new 海象或 new 行星或其他任何东西时
what Java is going to do is it's going to allocate a box of bits for each instance variable of the class--
Java 为类的每个实例变量分配一个盒子
here they are, listed--
在这里列出了...
and fill them with a default value, say, zero or null.
并用缺省值填充它们，比方说0或 null
And then the constructor will then usually fill every box with some other value.
然后构造函数通常会用其他值填充每个盒子
It doesn't have to.
并不全是这样
But in this case, it will.
但这种情况下是这样
So let's see an example.
让我们来看一个例子
So when I run this visualizer here,
在这里运行 visualizer
I will see that walrus, whenever I run the constructor--
每次运行构造函数时，我都会看到那只海象
once I call new, two boxes are created, one for the weight and one for the tusk size.
一旦调用 new，就会创建两个盒子，一个用于存储重量，另一个用于存储象牙大小
And they're filled in with a default value of 0.
并且缺省值都是0
Now the constructor will come through and reset them to some other value in this case,
本例中构造函数将它们重置为其他值
though it doesn't necessarily have to do that.
尽管不一定非要这么做
So whenever this code runs, what ends up happening,
每次运行这段代码时，最终会发生什么
what the new keyword does for us is it creates two boxes, one of size 32 bits, one of 64 bits, for a total of 96.
new 关键字为我们创建两个盒子，一个32位，一个64位，总共96位
So that's what happens when we instantiate an object.
这就是实例化一个对象时发生的事情
Now, it's interesting to actually reflect on what happens at the bit level.
此时在比特级别上发生的事情很有趣
Now this is a little beyond the scope of the class,
这有点超出了这门课的范围
but somehow I find it satisfying to know that this is approximately what's going on under the hood.
但我很乐于了解底层正在发生的事情
This is a little bit of a simplification,
这有点简化了
but in this case, whenever we call new, what Java will do is it will-- when I say new walrus,
每当调用 new 时，Java所做的时...执行 new Walrus() 时
it's going to dig through memory,
它会进入内存
and it's going to find 96 bits, because that's how many it needs to store the walrus.
找到96个位，因为这是它存储海象所需的区域
And then it's going to fill in those.
然后填满这些
The constructor will fill in this top bit with 1,000 and this bottom bit here, the blue bits, with 8.3.
构造函数用1000填充这个顶部区域，用8.3填充底部区域，就是蓝色的位
So this happens to be 8.3.
这恰好是8.3
And on a more physical level, that's a rough picture of what's going on.
这就是物理层面上发生的事情
Now, I'm going to admit this is a bit of a simplification.
我得承认这有点简单化了
The actual size of a walrus will be a little bit bigger than 96 bits, because there's various information that's header information or overhead up here,
海象实际比96位稍大一点，因为还要有各种信息，比如头部信息
but I'm not showing it here because it's just beyond the scope of our class, and this is good enough for us.
但不在这里展示，因为它超出了我们课程的范围，这对我们来说已经足够了
So in other words, what happens is your computer has a few billion bits.
换句话说，你的计算机有几十亿位
It looks through those bits, and it somehow decides, yes, this.
它浏览那些比特，然后决定存放在这里
This is the place where my walrus is going to live.
这就是海象将要生存的地方
Here is the weight.
这里是重量
Here is the tusk size.
这里是象牙的大小
And there it goes.
就是这样
So what's interesting about the new keyword
那么 new 关键字哪里有趣呢？
is that we can think of it not only as going out to this massive field of bits and finding a home for the information on the walrus,
我们不仅可以想象成从这片巨大的比特领域为海象找到归宿
but we can also think of it as reporting where it put the walrus.
还可以把它想象成报告了海象的位置
So if I go to the fields and I bury a treasure,
假如我去田里埋藏宝藏
I mean, that's great.
那可太棒了
The treasure's in the field now.
宝藏现在在田里了
But if I ever want to see that treasure again or let someone know where it is, I have to report that information,
但是如果我再想看到宝藏，或者让别人知道它在哪里，就必须报告这些信息
that out there in the corner of the field,
在田野的角落里
that's where the treasure is.
宝藏就在那里
So what'll happen is that the new keyword,
接下来，new 关键字
you could think of it as returning the value, or the number of bit in memory,
可以视为返回一个，值或内存中的位数
where it put the walrus.
海象存放的位置
So it's very natural.
这顺其自然
It's a sequence of bits that what new can just do is return,
这是一个比特序列，new 可以返回地址
OK, hey, you know where I put that wonderful walrus?
“嘿，你知道我把海象放哪儿了吗？”
I put it in bit number 2,384,723,423.
“我把它放在2,384,723,423位”
And that will be the so-called-- you can think of that as the return value of the new keyword.
这就是所谓的...你可以理解为 new 关键字的返回值
So it goes out there, it buries the treasure,
它表明这里埋藏了宝藏
then it shouts to the heavens, this is where I've put this treasure, this wonderful walrus.
“这就是我埋藏宝藏的地方，一只奇妙的海象”
So what?
怎么样？
Well, let's talk a little bit about the declaration of a variable that's a reference type.
让我们来讨论一下引用类型变量的声明
So before we've been talking about instantiation,
在讨论实例化之前
how new works, now let's talk about declaration.
讨论 new 是如何工作的
So if I have a piece of code that declares that a walrus exists or that a dog exists
如果我有一段代码声明海象或狗的存在
or that a planet exists, what Java will do is it will allocate a box of exactly 64 bits,
或者行星存在，Java 会分配一个恰好64位的盒子
no matter what type of object.
不管是什么类型的对象
It's a reference type.
它是一个引用类型
That's just what's going to happen.
这就是发生的事情
And then these bits can either be set to null, that is, all zeros,
然后这些位设置为null，即全0
or it scould be set to the address of a specific instance of that class as returned by new.
或者它可以设置为由 new 返回的特定实例的地址
So let's see this very simple example.
看一个简单的例子
If I say walrus, some walrus, and then say some walrus equals null, well,
Walrus somWalrus， 然后是 someWalrus = null
that first line, what it does is creates a box of 64 bits.
第一行创建一个64位的盒子
And the second line, equals null,
第二行
sets it all equal to zero as a marker to say,
将其全部设置为0作为标记
well, it's nothing. It's null.
意味着它是空的
By contrast, if I say walrus, some walrus--
相比之下，Walrus someWalrus
that creates a box of 64 bits--
产生了一个64位的盒子
and then say equals new walrus, then what's going to happen is that after new, goes out to the field,
然后 new Walrus()，它走到田野里
and it digs the hole and puts the delicious,
挖了个洞，把美味的...
delicious walrus-- that's not nice--
美味的海象...不太合适...
our lovely walrus in the field and then shouts, here's the location of the walrus.
把可爱的海象放在田野里，然后喊道：“这就是海象的位置”
This serves as a record of that information.
这就是该信息的记录
So if it got put in location 0100011 yada yada,
假如它被放在0100011号
that is going to be what we store in this box.
这就是储存在盒子里的东西
So even though the walrus itself is 96 bits,
所以即使海象本身有96位
the address that we store is 64 bits.
但我们存储的地址是64位
And it's just in a modern Java Runtime Environment,
在现代 Java 运行时环境中
64 bits is the size of the address.
64位是地址的大小
That's how many bits we use to represent this number right here.
也就是用来表示这个数字的位数
So while this notation does give us a fairly accurate picture of what's going on--
虽然这个符号准确地告诉我们发生的事情
and again, I kind of fudged things a little bit, and when you go to 61C or even an operating systems class,
再说一次我有点胡编乱造，当你去上 61C 甚至是操作系统课程时
you'll get a really more honest understanding.
你会得到更准确的理解
While this is good enough for our purpose in 61B,
虽然这对 61B 来说已经足够了
it's not particularly instructive to look at this giant stream of bits and expect to know anything.
这个冗长的比特流难以阅读
So what I'm going to do is similar to before.
所以和以前一样
We're not going to show explicitly the binary information shown in a memory box.
我们不会显式地写出内存盒子中的二进制信息
We're going to instead use this simplified box notation.
我们将改用简化盒子表示法
And in this case, whenever we're talking about reference types,
这种情况下，谈论引用类型时
this notation will often be called box and pointer.
此符号通常记为盒子和指针
OK, so what is it?
这是什么呢？
So whenever we have a null, a bunch of zeros,
每当我们有 null，也就是一堆0
we're just going to write null in the box,
只需在盒子中写 null
because having 64 zeros in a row is just a waste of space.
因为写连续64个0只是浪费空间
And if we ever have a non-zero address, that is-- sorry--
如果我们有一个非0的地址
that is, if this address is anything other than zeros,
也就是说如果地址不是0
then we're going to draw an arrow to whichever object the walrus is pointing at.
我们就要向海象所指的对象画一个箭头
So instead of showing this right here,
所以与其展示这个
this sequence of seemingly random 64 bits, we'll draw an address that shows us which walrus we're talking about.
这个看似随机的64位序列，我们将绘制一个地址，表明正在谈论的是哪只海象
So here is our 96-bit walrus.
这就是96位对应的海象
Here's our 64-bit box holding the address.
这是我们存放地址的64位盒子
And there's a pointer, hence the name box and pointer notation.
这里有一个指针，因此有了名字盒子和指针符号
You may not realize it, but you now know everything you need to solve the mystery of the walrus.
你可能没意识到，你现在知道了解开海象之谜所需的一切
So I mentioned the golden rule of equals, that equals just copies the bits.
我提到的等号的黄金法则，即等号只是复制比特
That's all it does.
仅此而已
Now, that's true for primitive types,
这对于基本类型是正确的
but it actually is also true for reference types and in fact,
对于引用类型也是如此
for any situation in Java where you say equals.
实际上对于 Java 中任何情况都一样
So in terms of our visual metaphor,
就视觉而言
what that means is we're going to copy the arrow by making--
这意味着我们要复制箭头...
if we say, for example, b equals a,
比如说 b = a
we're going to make the arrow in the b box point at the same instance as a.
b 盒子中的箭头应指向与 a 相同的实例
So let's see that in terms of box and pointer notation.
我们从盒子和指针符号的角度看这点
So when I say walrus a, what does that do?
Walrus a 是什么意思呢？
Well, that creates a box of 64 bits.
产生了一个64位的盒子
There it is.
就是这个
And I've only shown it very small.
我只展示了小部分
I mean, I could make huge box, but we know it's 64 bits,
也就是说我可以做个大盒子，但知道它是64位了
because look, it says so right there.
就可以这么写
Now when I say a equals new walrus,
执行 a = new Walrus() 时
the new keyword goes out to memory, finds the bits it needs, the 96 bits, and it shouts the location,
new 关键字进入内存，找到它需要的96位，并报告位置
which a will dutifully record.
a 负责记录地址
So this walrus is 96 bits.
所以这只海象96位
The new keyword yells the address.
new 关键字报告地址
We store the address here.
我们把地址存储在这里
And rather than writing out that 64-bit address,
而不是写出地址
we draw an arrow, because that's easier to understand.
我们画一个箭头，因为这样更容易理解
Next, up we say walrus b.
接下来执行 Walrus b
This creates a box, which is 64 bits.
这将创建一个64位的盒子
So both a and b are 64 bits.
a 和 b 都是64位
And at this point, b is not defined, right?
这时 b 还有没定义对吗？
It's not that it's null.
它不是 null
Right now, it's just nothing.
只是什么都没有
It's just some box of 64 bits.
它只是一个64位的盒子
Who knows what's in there?
谁知道里面是什么呢？
And when we say b equals a, we're going to copy that string of bits.
当执行 b = a 时，就要复制那串比特
Remember, there's 64 bits here.
记住，这里有64位
If we had the bit picture, it'd just be a string of 64 bits.
如果我们有位的图形，它就只是一个64位的字符串
We'll copy them into this box.
把它复制到这个盒子里
And so at that point, when we say b equals a,
所以此时，b = a 时
b is pointing at the same object.
b 指向同一个对象
So now, if we are to try and do something like b.weight,
现在如果我们尝试做一些像 b.weight 这样的事情
it's saying, follow the arrow.
它会说：“跟着箭头走”
Go to the walrus.
“去海象那儿”
You will find the information you seek.
“你会找到你要找的信息”
And in that case, you might say, b.weight equals something.
在这种情况下，你可能会让 b.weight 等于某个值
So I hope now it's clear why the mystery of the walrus is resolved the way it does.
希望你清楚为什么海象之谜这样解开
And that's all you need to know to understand the whole deal.
以上就是你需要理解的所有东西
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）